Finding Aid for the Will Connell Papers LSC.0893
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Salon prints, portraits of cats and dogs, some titled., Mostly mounted, 45 × 35cm, unless otherwise noted. (Box 9)
  - 38-41. On the window screen, Cat climbing up screen., 1929.; (4 copies, various sizes). (Box 9)
  - 42-44. Mustachio, Cat portrait., 1930.; (3 copies, various sizes). (Box 9)
  - 45. Face of black Scotch terrier, 1930. (Box 9)
  - 46. Scotch terrier with wood in mouth, 1932. (Box 9)
  - 47. Banshee - and the baby witches, Mother dog suckling pups., 1930. (Box 9)
- Portraits of Will Connell. Various sizes; unmounted unless otherwise noted. (Box 10)
- Portraits of local or famous personalites., Mounted, 45 × 35cm. unless otherwise noted. (Box 10)
  - (2) 1-2. Will Connell with Dorothy Lange and Ansel Adams at Asilomar, (Different views; 18 × 12.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 3. Connell talking to models, Griffith Park, Los Angeles, n.d.; (12.5 × 17cm.). (Box 10)
  - 4. Connell giving sign language instructions; probably Griffith Park, n.d.; (20 × 16.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 5. Connell and model on fence, Griffith Park, (16.5 × 20cm.). (Box 10)
  - 6. Connell, models and photographers in Griffith Park, (16.5 × 24.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 7. Connell and camera, Griffith Park, (12.5 × 16cm.). (Box 10)
  - 8. Connell taking photograph, Griffith Park, n.d.; (26.5 × 16.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 9. Connell and Frank Uhaus. Griffith Park, (28 × 24cm.). (Box 10)
  - 10. Connell squating by camera, n.d.; (20 × 25cm.). (Box 10)
  - 11. Connell smoking, (Photograph by Dick Ham)., n.d.; (Mounted, 25.5 × 23cm.). (Box 10)
  - 12. Connell working with transparency, n.d.; (25.5 × 20.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 13. Connell adjusting lights, n.d.; (24.5 × 19.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 14-17. Trick photography - Connell and animated camera, (4 photos, various sizes and poses). (Box 10)
  - 18. That fine critical gaze, Connell portrait., 1950.; (Mounted, 35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 19. Connell relazing in theater(?), n.d.; (35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 20. Connell and collegue at work (Connell wearing hat), (25 × 20.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 21. Connell atop dune. Red Rock Canyon, California, May 1, 1948.; (27 × 34.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 22. Connell with dixie cup outside stone building (apparently wilderness area) (Presentation photograph from E.A. Drake)., n.d.; (Mounted, 35 × 27cm.). (Box 10)
  - 23. Connell with camera at airport - sign on fence prohibits photography, n.d.; (Mounted, 35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 24. Connell, under wing of plane, kneeling by camera, (Mounted, 28 × 35cm.). (Box 10)
  - 25. Side angle view of Connell squating, sizing up airplane, n.d.; (Mounted, 35 × 28cm.). (Box 10)
  - 26. Will Connell, (Photograph by Larry Frost; Easter gift to Mr. and Mrs. Connell)., 1955.; Signed and mounted (35.5 × 28cm.). (Box 10)
  - 27. Just Will, Connell posing with lights., 1940.; (Mounted, 40 × 30.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 28. Will Connell, (Photograph by Phill Hanna; autographed by Connell for Ramsey Oppenheim)., 1928.; (Mounted, 45.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 29. 7th St. Studio. Connell checking proofs with collegues, n.d.; (Mounted, 45.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 30. Don Allen, Connell's nephew., 1934.; (Mounted, 45.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 31-34. Photographs of Will Connell's son Bill Connell., (All mounted, 45.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 10)
    - 31. Bill Connell, 1936. (Box 10)
    - 32. Bill Connell, peering over back of chair, 1936. (Box 10)
    - 33. Will Connell and son Will (Bill), [1936?]. (Box 10)
    - 34. Bill, 1937. (Box 10)
  - 35-41. Self-portraits, n.d.; (Included are various trick photography photos; some duplicates, various sizes). (Box 10)
  - 42. Connell, Portrait of Will Connell with name superimposed., n.d.; (35.5 × 27.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 43. Humerous self(?) portrait, n.d.; (34 × 27cm.). (Box 10)
  - 44. Manley P. Hall, 1928. (Box 10)
  - 45. Ralph Hamer, 1929. (Box 10)
  - (1) 46-47. Phil Hanna, 1928.; (2 copies). (Box 10)
  - (2) 48-49. Don Herold, 1931-32.; (3 copies, different dates). (Box 10)
  - 50-51. Katherine Herald, 1932.; (2 copies; no.9 has special touch-up job). (Box 10)
  - 52. Katherine Herald, 1930. (Box 10)
  - 53. Isabel Morse Jones. (This print was made in by Carolyn Jones from the original Connell negative)., 1963 (Box 10)
  - 54. Martha Ball Lane, 1933. (Box 10)
  - 55-57. A.B. McCallister, 1928.; (3 copies). (Box 10)
  - 58. Janet, (Janet McCarthy, Sunkist Ad for McCall's, 1932)., 1929. (Box 10)
  - 59. Janet, (Same child as no.16, slightly older)., 1929. (Box 10)
  - 60. J.P. Mayers, 1929. (Box 10)
  - (1) 61-62. José Rodriguez, 1929.; (2 portraits, different poses). (Box 10)
  - 63. Carl Sandburg, 1926(?) or 1927(?).; (Unmounted, 35.5 × 28cm.). (Box 10)
  - 63-64. Shackelford, 1928.; (2 copies). (Box 10)
  - (1) 65-66. Carl Smalley, 1931.; (2 portraits, different poses). (Box 10)
  - (2) 67-69. Father and son, 1928.; (3 copies). (Box 10)
  - (1) 70-71. Louis Treviso, n.d.; (2 copies). (Box 10)
  - 72. Dr. Don Wilson, 1936.; (Mounted, 33 × 35.5cm.). (Box 10)
  - 73-74. Ray Winters, 1928.; (2 copies). (Box 10)
- Scenic views - mountains and deserts, mainly California. Salon prints., Mounted (45 × 35cm.) unless otherwise noted. (Box 11)
- Architectural views - exterior and interior, domestic and public., Salon prints mounted (45 × 35cm.). (Box 11)
  - (1) 1-2. Mono Lake, 1930.; (2 copies). (Box 11)
  - 3. Ghost town, (Bodie, California)., 1930. (Box 11)
  - 4-5. Point Fermin Farm, 1932.; (2 copies, no.5 is dated 1931). (Box 11)
  - 6. Desert Hill, 1928. (Box 11)
  - 7. Desert Dawn, 1926. (Box 11)
  - 8. American Pastoral, (Salines River Valley, California)., 1929. (Box 11)
  - 9. The Bishop's Mitre, (Mt. San Luis Obispo)., 1931. (Box 11)
  - 10. In the Salines River Valley, 1930. (Box 11)
  - 11. Mt. San Jacinto, 1932. (Box 11)
  - 12. Fort Tejon, (Tehachapie Mountains)., 1930. (Box 11)
  - 13-14. Palm Springs, 1932.; (2 copies). (Box 11)
  - 15-16. West Fence, 1939.; (Southern Lompec Peninsula; 2 copies, no.16 larger, 40 × 45.5cm.). (Box 11)
  - 17. San Jacinto, 1928. (Box 11)
  - 18. Cajon Pass, 1931. (Box 11)
  - 19. Mt. San Bernadino, 1930. (Box 11)
  - 20. Desert Cloud Burst no.1, (Red Rock Canyon, California)., 1926. (Box 11)
  - 21. Desert Cloud Burst no.2, (Red Rock Canyon, California)., 1926. (Box 11)
  - 22. Snow in the near hills Los Angeles, 1932. (Box 11)
  - 23-24. Unidentified desert scenes, (different views)., 1930. (Box 11)
  - 25. Unidentified. Sheep climbing up hill, 1929. (Box 11)
  - 26. Unidentified rocky pass, 1927(?) or 1929(?). (Box 11)
  - 27. Ranch near San Luis Obispo, n.d.; (Mounted, 38 × 45.5cm.). (Box 11)
  - 28. Mt. San Jacinto, n.d.; (Mounted, 38 × 45.5cm.). (Box 11)
  - 29. Winter Sunshine, 1939.; (Mounted, 40 × 45.5cm.). (Box 11)
  - 30. Cajon Pass, n.d.; (Mounted, 40.5 × 47cm.). (Box 11)
  - 31-37. Frank Lloyd wright designs. (Box 11)
    - 31. Exterior design of office building, 1932. (Box 11)
    - 32. Exterior of Residence B, Barnsdall Park, built, 1921, 1928. (Box 11)
    - 33. Exterior of Hollyhock House, Barnsdall Park, 1927. (Box 11)
    - 34. Architectural motif for Barnsdall house, 1927. (Box 11)
    - 35. Exterior of Oasis Hotel, Palm Springs, built, 1925, 1927. (Box 11)
      Lloyd Wright
      [son]
    - 36. Exterior of Taggart house, Griffith Park, built, 1922, n.d. (Box 11)
    - 37. Interior of Navarro's house, built, 1926, n.d. (Box 11)
  - 38-44. Stores in Los Angeles: Art Deco designs. (Box 11)
    - 38. Exterior Desmonds, 1928. (Box 11)
    - 39. Exterior Sommer & Kaufman, 1930. (Box 11)
    - 40-42. Interior Sommer & Kaufman(?), 1930.; (3 photos). (Box 11)
    - 43-44. Interior Zachos(?), 1928.; (2 photos). (Box 11)
  - 45. Exterior Hollywood High School, 1929. (Box 11)
  - 46. Unidentified landscape view in Arrowhead Springs, California, 1929. (Box 11)
  - 47-48. Unidentified homes, Exterior views., 1931. (Box 11)
  - 49. Woman strolling through portico, 1930. (Box 11)
  - 50. View of roof taken through skylight, 1926. (Box 11)
  - 51. Exterior Breakers Club, 1929. (Box 11)
  - 52. Interior enclosed sunporch, 1929(?). (Box 11)
  - 53. Interior unidentified home, Early Spanish style., n.d. (Box 11)
  - 54. Interior unidentified home, looking through dining room, 1931. (Box 11)
  - 55. Interior unidentified home - living room, 1931. (Box 11)
  - 56. Unidentified hallway, n.d. (Box 11)
  - 57-58. Unidentified home - Art Deco sitting room, 1928.; (2 views). (Box 11)
  - 59. Interior unidentified home - stairway, 1935. (Box 11)
  - 60-62. Unidentified statue, 1928.; (Three copies; no.32 is trick effect). (Box 11)
- Salon prints, 38 × 48cm., on extra-heavy mounts. Miscellaneous subjects; many exhibited in the Art Directors Club Show (ACS), August 1962. (Box 12)
  - 1. Untitled. Man in pin-striped suit, 1945. (Box 12)
  - 2. Untitled. Mayonaise in the making: ingredients, eggbeater, and finished product product (Box 12)
  - 3. Backyard gossips, World War II Victory garden; portrait of Will Connell and wife by E.P. Cohen. (Box 12)
  - (1) 4-5. Farmer Kidson and carrots. The early days of the Los Angeles Farmers Market, (2 copies). (Box 12)
  - 6. Untitled. Unidentified beach scene, (Men wear bathing suit tops)., 1930's. (Box 12)
  - 7. Fighting cocks, Silver table pieces; apparent advertisement for Brooks., n.d. (Box 12)
  - 8. Bragging, Rooster on mailbox., 1940. (Box 12)
  - 9. Tower of the Golden Gate Bridge, San Francisco., (61 × 50.5cm.). (Box 12)
- Fashion models., Mounted, mainly 45 × 35cm. (Box 13)
- Portraits. Salon prints., Mounted (45 × 35cm.) unless otherwise noted. (Box 13)
  - 1. It's what you cover that counts, Model sunbathing., 1936.; (35.5 × 45.5cm.). (Box 13)
  - 2. Model in two-piece summer fundress on beach, 1938. (Box 13)
  - 3. Bullock's Wilshire, Model poised on bike., n.d. (Box 13)
  - 4-7. Hosiery advertisements. (Box 13)
    - 4. Model's legs in evening shoes, 1931. (Box 13)
    - 5. Advertisement for Mission Knit Hosiery, n.d.; (Made from photo no.4). (Box 13)
    - 6. Model's legs in slippers, gartens and hosiery, (Trick effect), 1932. (Box 13)
    - 7. Advertisement for Mission Knit Hosiery, n.d.; (Made from photo no.6). (Box 13)
  - 8. Model sitting on ottoman, smoking, 1938. (Box 13)
  - 9. Nude model posing on ottoman, n.d. (Box 13)
  - 10-12. Semi-nude model in various stages of dressing, 1938.; (3 portraits). (Box 13)
  - 13. #4 1938. Model, standing, adjusting cuffs of robe (Box 13)
  - 14. Model, seated, appling make-up, 1938. (Box 13)
  - 15-16. Model, dressed, posing in front of mirror, 1938.; (2 copies). (Box 13)
  - 17. Model seated in front of mirror, n.d. (Box 13)
  - 18. Close-up of model's foot, 1938. (Box 13)
  - 19-20. Model in formal gown, 1938.; (2 copies). (Box 13)
  - 21. Store sign advertisement for Mission Knit Hosiery., (Photo: 16.5 × 16cm.; mounted: 35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 13)
  - 22-24. Kenneth Alexander, 1932.; (3 photos, different poses). (Box 13)
  - 25. Merle Armitage, (Vignette profile)., 1929. (Box 13)
  - 26. Grace Marion Brown and Louis Samuels, 1932. (Box 13)
  - 27. H.S. Coberly, 1949.; (50 × 38cm.). (Box 13)
  - 28. Diedre and Bill Conselman, Jr., 1930. (Box 13)
  - 29. William Conselman, Jr., 1930. (Box 13)
  - 30-33. The Pale Lady, Mrs. Theodore B. Creamer., 1930.; (4 copies). (Box 13)
  - 34. Mrs. Theodore B. Creamer, (Vignette)., n.d. (Box 13)
  - 35. Pop Creamer, 1928. (Box 13)
  - 36-38. James M. Doolittle, 1929.; (3 photos, different poses). (Box 13)
  - 39. C.K. Eaton, 1936. (Box 13)
  - 40-41. Aries Fayer, 1928.; (2 copies). (Box 13)
  - 42. William Fostveth, 1931. (Box 13)
  - 43-44. Robert (Bob) Freeman, 1928.; (2 copies). (Box 13)
  - 45. Robert Freeman, 1938.; (38 × 45.5cm.). (Box 13)
  - 46-47. Fred Goudy, 1938.; (2 photos, different poses). (Box 13)
  - 48. Bertha (Mrs. Raymond) Griffith, 1931. (Box 13)
  - 49. Raymond (Ray) Griffith, 1929. (Box 13)
  - 50. Bertha and Raymond Griffith, 1933. (Box 13)
  - 51. Raymond and Mike Griffith, 1931. (Box 13)
  - 52. Bertha, Raymond and Mike Griffith, 1931. (Box 13)
- Unidentified portraits, mainly children. Salon prints., Mounted, 45 × 35cm. (Box 14)
- Miniatures., 11.5 × 9cm; mounted, 45 × 35cm. Miscellaneous photographs, mainly untitled. (Box 14)
  - 1-3. Chinese character, 1932.; (3 photos, different poses). (Box 14)
  - 4. Untitled. Small boys outside circus tent, 1926. (Box 14)
  - 5. Untitled. Crowd at circus sideshow, 1926. (Box 14)
  - 6. Unidentified blond model (Box 14)
  - 7. Unidentified model, seated, 1932. (Box 14)
  - 8. Mabs, 1934. (Box 14)
  - 9. Unidentified young man seated under modern art bust, 1928. (Box 14)
  - 10. Polo player, 1932. (Box 14)
  - 11. Miner, panning for gold, n.d. (Box 14)
  - 12. Desert Rat, Old man lighting a corncob pipe., 1926. (Box 14)
  - 13. Mamie, 1927. (Box 14)
  - 14-15. Helen, 1931. (Box 14)
  - 16. Donnie, 1934. (Box 14)
  - 17. The Irreducibles, Two small boys., 1929. (Box 14)
  - 18. Unidentified twin boys in doorway, 1927. (Box 14)
  - 19. Unidentified little boy with toothless grin, 1927. (Box 14)
  - 20. Unidentified little boy in a sweater, 1927. (Box 14)
  - 21. Little girl in a rocking chair, 1930. (Box 14)
  - 22-23. Whistling boy, 1931.; (2 copies). (Box 14)
  - 24. Young girl with bobbed hair, profile, 1929. (Box 14)
  - 25. Little blond girl with ribbon in hair (Box 14)
  - 26. Child with cat, n.d. (Box 14)
  - 27. Baby with doll, 1931. (Box 14)
  - 28-29. Baby holding dress, 1928.; (2 copies). (Box 14)
  - 30. Baby with rattle, 1930. (Box 14)
  - 31. Baby in undershirt, 1931. (Box 14)
  - 32. Movie theatre in the night rain, 1929. (Box 14)
  - 33. Bowl of flowers behind glass of orange juice, (Color photograph). (Box 14)
  - 34-35. Pouring the mold, 1929.; (2 copies; no.3 on bronze metallic paper, no.4 on silver). (Box 14)
  - 36. Tiered, stacked metal cylinders on silver metallic paper, 1929. (Box 14)
  - 37. Infant's silverware, 1929. (Box 14)
  - 38. Ornate tea service, 1929. (Box 14)
  - 39. Tea pot and dish, 1930. (Box 14)
  - 40. Silver vases, 1929. (Box 14)
  - 41-42. Carolyn, 1927.; (2 photos, different poses). (Box 14)
  - 43. Maidenhood, 1923.; (Bromoil transfer). (Box 14)
  - 44. Alice, 1923.; (Bromoil transfer). (Box 14)
  - 45. Child and chair, 1929. (Box 14)
  - 46. Child at head of stairs, 1929. (Box 14)
  - 47. Rear portrait of model, 1929. (Box 14)
  - 48. Phil Hanna, 1928. (Box 14)
    (See also Box 16)
  - 49. Lloyd Wright, 1929. (Box 14)
- Salon Print. Miscellaneous photographs, many from exhibits., Mounted; 45 × 35 unless otherwise noted. (Box 15)
- Untitled advertisement photographs., Mounted, 45 × 35cm. (Box 15)
  - 1-3. Ice cube, 1932.; (3 photos, different views; no.3 is split sulfide and blue-toned). (Box 15)
  - 4-8. Figurines. (Box 15)
    - 4-6. Quartet, 1929.; (2 photos, different angles). (Box 15)
    - 7-8. Quartet in front of window, 1928.; (2 copies; no.8 an enlargement, different date: 1929). (Box 15)
  - 9. The Hayden Trio, Marionettes., 1930. (Box 15)
  - 10. Female marionette, n.d. (Box 15)
  - 11-12. Car approaching train underpass, 1937(?).; (2 copies; unmounted, 27.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 15)
  - 13-16. Underpass, 1937.; (4 copies, various sizes; no.16 unmounted). (Box 15)
  - 17. Young America, Model airplane devotees., 1943. (Box 15)
  - 18. Lighted window (Box 15)
  - 19-20. Giraffe statue and shadow, 1928.; (2 copies, no.19 unmounted 28.5 × 22.5cm.). (Box 15)
  - 21. Electrical controls reflected in mirror, 1931. (Box 15)
  - 22. Ornate cabinet, 1930. (Box 15)
  - 23-24. Futility, Model wearing mask., 1927.; (2 photos, different poses). (Box 15)
  - 25-26. Navel parade, Chorus line., 1936.; (2 copies, different dates: no.26, 1933). (Box 15)
  - 27. City Views, 1932. (Box 15)
  - 28. Portrait of Los Angeles, 1932.; (Apparent duplicate of no.27). (Box 15)
  - 29. Gallantry, 1927. (Box 15)
  - 30. Cactus plants in pot, 1930. (Box 15)
  - 31. Rain on quiet waters, 1945.; (40.5 × 50.5cm.). (Box 15)
  - 32-35. Nescafé ads with celebrities, n.d. (Box 15)
    - 32. Hugh Herbert. (Box 15)
    - 33. Joan Bennett. (Box 15)
    - 34. Anne Rutherford. (Box 15)
    - 35. Joan Davis. (Box 15)
  - 36. Unidentified man drinking warm beverage, (Not specified if Nescafé). (Box 15)
  - 37-43. Avocado ads. (Box 15)
    - 37. Avocado half on lettuce, 1931. (Box 15)
    - 38-39. Avocado half on lettuce, 1932. (Box 15)
    - 40. Avocado half on endive, 1932. (Box 15)
    - 41. Coloro, 1933.; (Apparent duplicate of no.9, despite discrepancy of dates). (Box 15)
    - 42-43. Avocado slices on tomato and lettuce, 1932. (Box 15)
  - 44-48. Silver ads. (Box 15)
    - 44. Gravy boat, pitcher, and spoons, 1930. (Box 15)
    - 45. Tea service on tray, n.d. (Box 15)
    - 46-47. Fighting cocks, 1930.; (2 copies). (Box 15)
    - 48. Decorative plate, 1929. (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous photographs., Mounted (45 × 35cm.) unless otherwise noted. (Box 16)
- Salon prints. Various subjects, many with special or trick effects., Mounted, 45 × 35cm. (Box 16)
- Advertisement photographs., Mounted (45 × 35cm.) unless otherwise noted. (Box 16)
  - 1-15. Photographs of soapbubbles, n.d.; (no.1-5 unmounted, 36 × 28cm.; no.6 unmounted, 29.5 × 24.5cm.). (Box 16)
  - 16-17. Water spray, Garden hose watering lawn., 1932.; (2 copies). (Box 16)
  - 18. Crowded intersection, n.d.; Photograph in rhomboidial shape. (Box 16)
  - 19. Object with holes, 1930.; Special effects photograph. (Box 16)
  - 20. Parallel lines of small knobs, 1929. (Box 16)
  - 21. Tea pot, n.d..; Special effects photograph. (Box 16)
  - 22. Cactus plant, 1930. (Box 16)
  - 23. Postscript, Couple in empty theatre., 1927. (Box 16)
  - 24. Trumpet superimposed over another instrument, 1931. (Box 16)
    Now in Box 38.
  - 25-27. Tuba player, 1935.; Special effects photograph; title illegible (3 copies, dates vary: 1935, 1937). (Box 16)
  - 28-29. Insignia for the club, 1936. (Box 16)
  - 30. Three light bulbs, 1930. (Box 16)
  - 31. Pattern of running camels, 1930. (Box 16)
  - 32-36. Eyeglasses, 1929-1935.; Various special effects. (Box 16)
    2 photographs removed, now in Box 37.
  - 37. Unidentified industrial worker, Special effects photograph. (Box 16)
  - 38-41. Champagne glasses, 1930-31.; Various special effects. (Box 16)
  - 42-49. Chevrolet montages, 1938.; (8 photos, various special effects; no.1-3 unmounted, 35 × 41cm.; no.4-8 mounted, 38 × 44cm.). (Box 16)
    1 mounted item now in Box 38.
  - 50. Food ad, n.d.; Special effect with eyeglasses. (Box 16)
  - 51. California in the palm of your hand, Radio advertisement., 1936. (Box 16)
  - 52. The phantom audience, Radio ad., 1936. (Box 16)
  - 53. Portrait of J.W., Santa Fe cigar ad., 1932. (Box 16)
  - 54. Untitled. Man smoking a cigar, (Apparent duplicate of no.12 despite discrepancy of dates)., 1934. (Box 16)
  - 55. Untitled Santa Fe cigar ad, Man and barber. (Box 16)
  - 56. Untitled Santa Fe cigar ad, Nautical photo., 1932. (Box 16)
  - 57. Untitled nautical photograph, n.d.; (Similar to no.15: same pose, no cigar). (Box 16)
  - 58-59. Fashion montage, 1937; (2 copies). (Box 16)
    Item 59 now in Box 38.
- Early color prints, Portfolio no.1., Mounted (45 × 35cm.) unless otherwise noted. (Box 17)
- Early color prints, Portfolio no.2., Mounted (45 × 35cm.) unless otherwise noted. (Box 17)
  - 1-2. Russet lady in floppy hat, 1934.; (2 copies; no.2: 35 × 27cm., undated). (Box 17)
  - 3. Joshua trees, spring flowers, 1935.; (37.5 × 30.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 4. Yucca blossoms, (This photograph by Steve Hanson)., n.d. (Box 17)
  - 5-6. Horseman paper cut-outs, n.d.; (2 photos). (Box 17)
  - 7-8. Blonde girl with pale green satin blouse, 1935.; (2 photos). (Box 17)
  - 9-11. Christmas doll, n.d.; (3 photos; no.9: 36 × 28.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 12. Blonde child with hands touching above head (Box 17)
  - 13. Coffee set on damask tablecloth, 1935. (Box 17)
  - 14. Child in pink hat and coat (Box 17)
  - 15-17. Model in long red dinner dress, 1938.; (3 copies; no.15-16: unmounted, 35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 17)
    (See also Box 19)
  - 18-20. Model in negligee, standing in front of mirror, 1938.; (3 copies; no.18-19: unmounted, 35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 21-23. Model in negligee, sitting in fornt of mirror, 1938.; (3 copies; unmounted, 35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 24. Model in nightgown before mirror, 1938.; (Unmounted, 35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 25-26. Girl in flowered gown, 1938.; (2 copies, no.25 unmounted, 33 × 24.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 27-34. Hosiery ad(?), 1938.; (8 photos, 2 different poses; no.28-30, unmounted, 35 × 27.5 cm.; no.31-34, 27.5 × 35cm.). (Box 17)
  - 35-36. Scotch and soda set up (Box 17)
  - 37. Steffi Duna, Spanish se orita, (Photo by Clendenin and Hansen)., 1936. (Box 17)
  - 38. Se or and se orita, (Photo by Clendenin and Hansen) no.37-38 from the movie Dancing Pirates by Warner Brothers, 1936. 1936. (Box 17)
  - 39. Artist Paul Sample and wife Sylvia, in his studio, 1935. (Box 17)
  - 40. Pinapple salad, silverized background, (Unmounted, 20 × 25.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 41-42. Orange juice and flowers, 1932.; (2 copies). (Box 17)
  - 43. Montage, All Year Club, 1937. (Box 17)
    (See also Box 27)
  - 44. Blue In-Plant shot, n.d. (Box 17)
  - 45. Rooster on mailbox, n.d. (Box 17)
  - 46. Vulture(?), n.d. (Box 17)
  - 47. Marionettes, n.d. (Box 17)
  - 48-49. Child drinking orange juice, 1934.; (2 photos; no.1, 28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 50. Max Factor make-up, n.d.; (26.5 × 30cm.). (Box 17)
  - 51. Claifornia poppies, 1938(?).; (35 × 26.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 52-53. Grapes, n.d.; (2 photos). (Box 17)
  - 54-55. Fruit salad, n.d.; (2 photos). (Box 17)
  - 56. Mickey Rooney in Out West with the Hardys, 1938.; (36 × 26cm.). (Box 17)
  - 57-58. Terrazo tile floor, n.d.; (2 photos, 35.5 × 41.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 59. Elderly model with patchwork quilt, n.d.; (Unmounted, 33 × 25cm.). (Box 17)
  - 60-61. Sweat Pea Maestro, n.d.; (2 photos, different views; no.14 untitled). (Box 17)
  - 62. Mother and small boy with daffodils, 1936.; (33 × 25.5cm.). (Box 17)
  - 63. Mother and small boy with pussywillows (Box 17)
  - 64. Girl singing into CBS microphone, n.d. (Box 17)
  - 65-69. Cut-outs by Grace Brown, n.d.; (5 photos, various views and sizes). (Box 17)
- Untitled salon prints on extra-heavy mounts. Many exhibited in the Art Directors Club Show (ACS) Chiefly, August 1962. undated. (Box 18)
  - 1. Testing steel gages under optical flats., (50 × 61cm.). (Box 18)
  - 2. Silver pitcher, gravy-boat, and spoons., (50.5 × 61cm.). (Box 18)
  - 3. World War II backyard Victory Garden, Los Angeles. Photo by E.P. Cohen., (61 × 50.5cm.). (Box 18)
    (See also Box 12)
  - 4. Richfield Oil Company, Catalytic Cracking Plant (tower only)., 1944.; (50.5 × 61cm.). (Box 18)
  - 5. Richfield Oil Company. Catalytic Cracking Plant., (50.5 × 61cm.). (Box 18)
  - 6. Tuba player., (61 c 50.5cm.). (Box 18)
  - 7. Unidentified man in shower. (Lou Nova?)., (50.5 × 61cm.). (Box 18)
  - 8. Two glasses of lemonade. Sunkist advertisement., (61 × 50.5cm.). (Box 18)
  - 1. Fruit salad., (50.5 × 61cm.). (Box 19)
  - 2-3. Man sneezing, 1945.; (Different views; no.2: 61 × 50.5, no.3: 50.5 × 61cm.). (Box 19)
  - 4. Nursery school children at lunch., (50.5 × 61cm.). (Box 19)
  - 5. Advertisement for Korbel champagne. Will Connell's hand poping cork off bottle. Photo by Frank Uhaus won an award of merit at ACS, 1962.; (50.5 × 61cm.). (Box 19)
  - 6. World War II - Calship, Los Angeles Harbor., (50.5 × 61cm.). (Box 19)
  - 7. Richfield Oil Company Alkylation unit., (61 × 50.5cm.). (Box 19)
  - 8. Richfield Oil Refinery., (61 × 50.5cm.). (Box 19)
  - 9. Richfield Oil Refinery(?)., (61 × 50.5cm.). (Box 19)
- Miscellaneous views and portraits., Mounted prints, 45 × 35.5cm., unless otherwise noted. Chiefly untitled. (Box 20)
  - 1. Lloyd Wright, 1929. (Box 20)
  - 2. Portrait of man with a moustache, resting right arm over back of chair(?) and holding with left hand, 1931. (Box 20)
  - 3. Portrait of a man and a woman (same man as in no.2), 1931. (Box 20)